let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following clocks was the first clack to measure time?",
    answer: "Sundail",
    options: [
      "Sundail",
      "Water Clock",
      "Sand Clock",
      "Quartz Clock"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "If oscilaion is 30 Hz then how many times the pendulum will oscilate per second?",
    answer: "30 Times",
    options: [
      "60 Times",
      "40 Times",
      "30 Times",
      "15 Times"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following clocks can measure time in <b> Nanoseconds </b>?",
    answer: "Atomic Clock",
    options: [
      "Mechanical Clock",
      "Digital Clock",
      "Atomic Clock",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is a not <b> Scalar Quantity </b>?",
    answer: "Force",
    options: [
      "Mass",
      "Force",
      "Length",
      "Time"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The <b>  Speedometer </b> in vehicles display the ___________ of the Vehicle?",
    answer: "Speed",
    options: [
      "Fuel Level",
      "Speed",
      "Distance",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },

 {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Convert 10 Celcius into Fahrenhiet. Which is the correct option of the following Question?",
    answer: "50 Fahrenhiet",
    options: [
      "45 Fahrenhiet",
      "32 Fahrenhiet",
      "50 Fahrenhiet",
      "49 Fahrenhiet"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following Thermometers are used to measure Weather?",
    answer: "Maximum-Minimum Thermometer",
    options: [
      "Maximum-Minimum Thermometer",
      "Clinical Thermometer",
      "Laboratory Thermometer",
      "Digital Thermometer"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The process of transfer of heat from hotter end to the cooler end of an object is called __________ ?",
    answer: "Conduction",
    options: [
      "Radiation",
      "Convection",
      "Conduction",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The interval between to events is known as  ___________?",
    answer: "Time",
    options: [
      "Measurement",
      "Time",
      "Distance",
      "Speed"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "___________ is defined as the rate of change of displacement? ",
    answer: "Velocity",
    options: [
      "Velocity",
      "Uniform Motion",
      "Non-Uniform Motion",
      "Speed"
    ]
  },



];